Huh?!
Wait, are you saying you
have a thing for Misuzu?!
Hell no.
You know we went out for a
while in middle school, right?
Huh?
Why didn't they tell me about this before?
Aren't they my best friends?
Best Bud's Secret
"Best Bud's Secret."
Hey, Misuzu!
What's this about you going out
with Jun in middle school?!
He finally let it slip, did he?
Why would you do that?!
You know how I feel about Jun, don't you?!
I didn't back then.
You didn't tell me you liked Junichiro until
right before we graduated middle school.
S-Still! If we were best friends,
you could've told me you had a boyfriend!
Both Junichiro and I wanted
to forget about it.
Besides, we didn't even
have time to tell you.
Huh?
Because we were only a couple for three days.
Three days?!
Now that you know, I might
as well tell you everything.
It was in the spring of our
second year of middle school.
He just asked me out of nowhere...
Gundo, would you...
maybe try going out with me?
That sounds like fun.
Even back then, a lot of girls
liked him for some reason,
so I kinda wanted to show him off.
Th-That was all it took?
Call it youthful indiscretion, I guess.
I started to feel like I was
reaching my limit the next day.
The next day?!
It was the day of our first date.
He invited me to go cycling with him,
so I agreed without giving
it much thought, and...
So... how far are we going?
We're almost there!
We repeated that exchange for two hours
while traveling forty kilometers one way.
Well?! Awesome view, right?!
View?
Are you a total moron?
Huh?
He dragged me all around again the next day.
I lost five kilograms in two days.
Uh... What was so bad about that?
You two are insane.
I had hit my limit both
physically and mentally,
so after the break, I approached
him to call it quits.
But then he said...
Sorry, Misuzu.
Huh?
I know this sounds weird when I'm
the one who asked you out, but...
I feel like maybe we're not
a good match after all.
So let's just give up on going out, okay?
He... beat me to it!
He put a permanent black mark on my life.
I'll never forgive him for it.
A lot of things suddenly make sense now.
So... you don't have any feelings
for Jun anymore, right?
Oh, I have feelings for him.
And all of them are hate.
I-I see...
A-Also, when you guys were
going out, did you... er, you know...
k-k-k-k...
kiss or anything?
The fact that we didn't share any mucosal
contact is our one silver lining.
Don't describe it as mucosal!
Well, if I had to say how far...
We called each other by our given names
and held hands while walking
to and from school.
But nothing major, really.
Feel better?
Yeah, I guess...
But I don't feel like I've been
discussing a relationship at all.
You told Tomo about us, didn't you?
I did plan to tell her eventually.
Yeah, yeah. Sorry.
It's fine.
Anyway, I didn't notice since I was
trying my hardest to forget it,
but you avoided Tomo for pretty much the
entire first year of middle school, didn't you?
I'll spare you all my questions about why.
But the time when you two went
back to being best friends
happened to be right when
you and I broke up.
Was that a coincidence?
I was entirely to blame for
everything that happened.
If you're mad about it,
it's not too late to hit me.
So there really was something going on.
Hit me all you want!
There's really nothing between
you and Misuzu anymore, right?
Really nothing?
I told you there's nothing.
How many times are you gonna ask?
Well, I was the only one
who didn't know about it!
I'm sorry, okay?
Okay, then...
Is there anyone you like now?
Huh? Of course not.
Really?
Yes, really. What's with you?
Oh, okay! As long as there isn't anyone!
There isn't!
Huh?
O-Okay...
I get it.
Morning, Aizawa-san!
Oh, hey, Misaki-senpai.
Misaki?
Wait, he's a guy.
Oh, yeah! Senpai, this here is Jun!
Oh!
Hi! I'm Misaki Kosuke, second-year.
Nice to—
What'd you do that for?!
Sorry. Reflex.
That wasn't a reflex!
I'm Kubota Junichiro. Sorry for what I did.
I-It's okay. No hard feelings here.
I hear you do karate?
Huh? Yeah.
Let's have a match sometime, then.
I'll crush you with every
ounce of strength I have.
Cru...
I'm so sorry, Senpai!
I'll give him a good talking-to!
That hurts, Tomo...
Can't breathe...
R-Really, it's okay. You can let him go.
Tomo... Hey...
Why are you so close to the
captain of the boys' club?
Aren't you in the girls' club?
Oh, I didn't tell you?
Stuff happened, and I'm
in the boys' club now.
What a disappointment.
The heir to the Aizawa style,
learning karate in school...
And what about you, Jun-bo?
I'll be sticking with you, sir!
Well said!
Wh-What's wrong?
Tomo, let's head home.
Sorry, I promised to get tea with
Misuzu and Carol after school.
Oh, come on! Don't pout!
I'm not pouting.
Yes, you are!
Tomorrow, okay? I'll walk
home with you tomorrow.
Tomorrow, then. You'd better stick to that.
Sure!
They're not dating, right?
That's right. Ridiculous, aren't they?
Uenomizu
High
School
I... I can't believe I ran into him here!
Senpai's scared of me now
'cause you threatened him!
Next time you see him,
smooth it out! Got it?!
So you live this way, huh?
Yeah. I usually ride my bike,
but it's in for repairs right now.
And that's why you're taking
the bus today, huh?
Yeah.
Why are you standing so far away?
I-It's just your imagination!
Y-You don't want to join
the karate club, Jun-kun?
No.
I see... S-Sorry for asking.
I don't think I could beat Tomo, anyway.
That's another reason I don't
want to join the club.
I don't want to lose.
But Aizawa-san was saying there
was no way she could beat you.
That's just at her dad's dojo.
When there are actual rules
to follow, I don't stand a chance.
I can manage to beat her in a fight, though.
Fight? You mean you and
Aizawa-san just... punch each other?
Yeah, sometimes.
You can't do that!
Aizawa-san is a girl, you know!
It's not like I want to hurt Tomo.
She's the problem.
Whenever we fight,
she comes after me for real.
Well... I can see why you would feel
like your life was in danger, but...
If I can beat her in a contest of strength,
it's only because I'm a guy.
In a sport with fixed rules,
I'm still the challenger.
I see. She is pretty incredible, isn't she?
Too incredible.
I still wish I could be like her.
As I am now...
I see. He looks up to
Aizawa-san, just like me.
That makes me feel a sort
of kinship with him.
Oh, I get the feeling I just said a
lot of weird stuff without thinking.
If you go blabbing to Tomo...
I-I won't! I swear I won't!
Never mind! He's still scary!
I heard you took the same
bus home as Jun yesterday.
He didn't threaten you again, did he?
No, it was fine.
We talked a bit, and he
was actually pretty nice.
Yes! He really is!
I'm so glad you get it!
He started acting weirdly intimidating
around our second year of middle school,
and he couldn't make any friends.
I tried introducing him to
some guys I knew, but...
Rrrr...
They were all too scared
of him to be his friend.
I knew you'd understand him, though!
You're not like all those wusses!
I can't tell her that I'm
actually terrified of him.
Jun is a super nice guy,
but he doesn't see me as a girl at all.
Would it kill him to be
a little considerate?
Huh?
Actually, I think he probably knows.
I mean, he—
Senpai!
Looks like you two are
having fun. Can I join in?
S-Sorry...
I'm sorry!
They're such good friends now!
Let's Go
on a Date!
"Let's Go on a Date!"
So, be honest... What do
you think of Aizawa Tomo?
L-Like, whatever.
I mean, she's a girl.
She even, like, wears a skirt.
I know, right? That skirt is just wrong!
No matter how boyish she looks...
Hey!
It's Mifune and Ogawa!
What a coincidence!
You guys come here a lot, too?
Sh...
She's wearing pants!
She's wearing, like, pants!
That's just wrong!
So, like, not fair...
What's wrong?
Those two should've joined us.
Why'd they just leave?
Because you're dressed like that.
More importantly, have you hung
out with Junichiro recently?
You haven't, have you?
We've barely hung out since we
started high school, actually.
He invites me out now and then,
but I get weirdly self-conscious.
You pick the most inconvenient
times to be all girly.
If you put him off too much,
he might find someone else
to spend his time with.
I don't want that!
Then you should be the one
to invite him out next time.
But not to the bowling alley or
batting center like you always do.
Wh-What's wrong with those?
Everything.
Why don't you act like students and go
shopping for clothes or do karaoke for once?
Me and... Jun?
That feels so unnatural.
Try inviting him yourself
over our next break.
You've kept him waiting
in place for so long,
I bet he'll come running
to you wagging his tail.
C'mon, he's not a dog.
Hey, Jun...
Over our next break...
if you're free, I mean...
Do you want to, um...
go hang out with me somewhere?
For real?!
Huh?
Oh, man, it's been forever!
Where? Where are we gonna go?!
Well, Tomo? Where are we gonna go?
H-He really is just a big dog!
You get it, right?
You can't think of it as just hanging out.
You're going on a date.
R-Right!
So...
Can I go, too?
Just kidding!
We'll go buy you some clothes after school.
You only own boys' clothes, right?
Huh? What I have should be fine.
Absolutely not.
Hey, Tomo-chan.
Saying you'll go on a date in
boys' clothes is a joke, right?
Fine. I'll go buy something.
What kind of outfit should we get?
Let's see... Maybe we should
start with something boyish?
Really? Not something girlish?
If we do that,
she'll be too uncomfortable
to think about the date.
Besides, he'd probably take off
running the moment he saw her.
So taking her from "a boy at first glance"
to "a girl with some boyish
features" is the way to go.
That sounds like a pain.
You got that right.
What kinds of shoes do you have, again?
Well, uh...
All I have are sneakers.
A red pair and a white pair...
I think white would be better.
I agree.
How about a simple, boyish outfit
that's sporty but a little girlish?
Let's go with that.
What do you think?
Huh?! Oh, uh, let's do that, then.
Oh! How about denim gaucho pants?
A white pullover would
probably go best with that.
I-Is fashion this hard to keep up with?
Thanks for helping me out, both of you.
I'll do something to thank you.
You don't need to worry about that.
I only did what I could as your best friend.
We're friends, aren't we?
You guys...
Just tell us every last detail of
everything that happens on your date,
and we'll call it even.
Looking forward to it!
R-Right...
I think they just formed a
powerful new tag team.
Sorry, Jun. Were you waiting long?
What's wrong?
Okay, well, shall we go?
Y-Yeah.
Batting Center
Man, it's been ages
since the last time I came here with you!
Shoot...
This is just turning out like the usual.
Wait, isn't this the spot where the
pitches can hit 160 kilometers per hour?
Yeah. That's about the speed
I've been hitting lately.
We were both hitting at 120 kilometers
per hour not long ago...
There's no way I can hit 160.
Try hitting one, Tomo.
Nice batting!
Tanaka Bowling
We haven't been here in ages, either.
We're just following the
same plan we used to!
Dude!
That one's 16 pounds!
Yeah. This is what I've been using lately.
He was using a lighter ball before.
I can't even lift one that heavy.
Wanna try this one out?
Strike!
No! I gotta change something up!
H-Hey, you wanna do karaoke
or something next?
Sure, why not?
I guess not, huh? But, y'know, every once in a—
Wait, what?!
Huh, so this is how it works?
I thought a place like this
would be... louder and busier.
This room is so small and dark.
Go on. Sit next to him.
Get all up against him!
What's wrong?
Aren't you gonna sing?
Sing?! No way in hell I'm gonna sing!
Why did we come here, then?
W-Well, why did you agree
to come here so quickly?
You never cared about karaoke before.
'Cause you said you wanted to go.
Huh?
Ever since we were kids, you only
ever wanted to do reckless stuff.
Frankly, I just let you coerce
me into going along at first,
but I was scared out of my mind.
You were?!
But when I just tried doing what
you asked, it was always fun.
That's why you're the best!
That's right... Jun just came
along today to have fun.
Yet I've been...
I can't keep going like this!
I gotta do something,
Oh, gonna sing something?
or this whole day will be ruined!
The Rolling Acorn
I can't sit around being embarrassed!
Roll, roll, roll, went the acorn...
Right into the pond! Oh, no!
Along came a loach, saying, "Hello there!"
"Come play with me, little one!"
Huh?
You're up next!
Don't laugh!
Sorry... That just wasn't
what I expected at all.
But seriously, a children's song?
You really are the best!
Sh-Shut up, you jerk!
So when Junichiro wasn't willing to sing,
you just sang children's songs
for three hours and went home?
I was so embarrassed, I thought I'd die!
He even shot a video of me!
It sounds like it went great, though.
I'm not so sure. Sounds like the
wrong way to have fun to me.
I guess I should delete the video.
Junichiro.
Huh?
Show us the video.
You guys!
"Come play with me, little one!"
That whole day, there was...
Hey! Why are you filming me?!
...something different about her.
My feelings drift through the starry sky,
so far away...
She's a natural...
They won't reach you, but...
You're so good, Misuzu-chan!
Bounce with me, bounce with me
All the sanity is sin, sin, sin here
She's so good at singing in English!
Bounce with me, bounce with me
I almost forgot she wasn't Japanese.
Move it down, up, down, up,
keepin' it up, boys...
Boom, boom! Boom, boom! Boom, boom!
Your turn, Tomo-chan.
Well, you're up, Queen of Children's Songs.
P-Please spare me!
The cat scratched me, the cat scratched me,
the cat was startled and scratched me!
I stepped on the cat, I stepped on the cat,
I stepped on the cat, and it scratched me!
The cat scratched me, the cat scratched me,
the cat was startled and scratched me!